Evi Nur Annisa

Jl. Pangeran Wirosobo, Yogyakarta 55162

<u>evinurannisa00@gmail.com</u> <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/evinannisa</u> https://evinannisa.github.io/eviannisa

Summary

Hello, my name is Evi Nur Annisa. I am a dedicated and creative Frontend Developer with a strong focus on designing and developing responsive web applications. With expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and frameworks like React and Next, I strive to build user-centered interfaces that deliver great user experiences. My approach blends innovation and attention to detail, resulting in visually appealing and well-performing solutions. I enjoy working in close collaboration and am always interested in exploring and applying the latest technologies to improve web development. Also, I am still growing and striving to be a better Evi each day. Take your time, check my resume and see my skills. Thank you.

Education

AMIKOM YOGYAKARTA UNIVERSITY

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Sep 2019 - Sep 2022

Diploma, Informatics Engineering

- GPA 3.82
- Teaching/Practicum Assistant
- Awarding Amikom Computer Club
- Committee of Penggalian Potensi Mahasiswa
- 3rd place Design UI/UX at "Gelar Karya Mahasiswa D3 Fakultas Ilmu Komputer Universitas Amikom Yogyakarta"

Work Experience

PT. Infosys Solusi Terpadu (IST) Frontend Developer (Fulltime)

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Feb 2023 – Present

- Build banking web application, create stable and consistent website according to design, integrate with APIs, reusable code, refactor code, fixing issue, etc
- Developing web applications with react typescript/javascript, styled components, tailwind css, material UI, SCSS, atomic design and module federation (micro frontend architecture)
- Collaborated with team to implement new feature developments

PT. Infosys Solusi Terpadu (IST) Frontend Developer (Bootcamp)

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Oct 2022 – Feb 2023

• Build project web application based with react is and material UI

- Work with UI/UX designers and backend developers to integrate designs and functionality
- Collaborated with team to implement project

PT. Media Kreasi Abadi (MKA)

Balikpapan, Indonesia

Feb 2022 – July 2022

Frontend Developer (Internship Kampus Merdeka)

- Learn frontend basics developers such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Using Version Control (git), Build Tools, Layouting and more
- Building web-based applications with React TypeScript and Pure CSS
- Collaborated with team members to develop a "parenting" website and research issues related to it.

PT. Geschool Cerdas Mandiri (GCM) Frontend Developer (Internship)

Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Sep 2021 – Jan 2022

- Implemented website landing pages from concept through deployment
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments

Amikom Yogyakarta University Practicum Assistant of Web Design 1

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Feb 2021 – Aug 2021

- Practice and explain HTML, CSS and JavaScript modules to students
- Reviewing lessons or lectures with students on a one-on-one basis or in small groups
- Supervising students in class and tracking attendance, grading assignments and calculating activity score

Leadership & Activities

BEM KM Amikom Yogyakarta University Ministry of Advocacy

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Feb 2021 – Feb 2022

- Capture the aspirations of all Amikom students
- Oversee internal and external issues on campus
- Establish communication with the Chancellor regarding student welfare needs
- Pioneer of the vaccination program, scholarship and all aspirations for Amikom students

Himpunan Mahasiswa Diploma Teknik Informatika Treasurer

Yogyakarta, Indonesia Sep 2020 – Dec 2021

- Oversee the general financial management of an organizing committee
- Plan and keep track of budgets within the organization, collect, deposit and keep track of funds write cheques and provide financial reports regularly

Portfolio

• Portofolio:

https://evinannisa.github.io/eviannisa

• Platform Education Parenting:

https://github.com/Media-Kreasi-Abadi/frontend-tim-j-batch-2

• Login page geschool:

https://madrasahdiy.net . http://gunungkidul.geschool.net . http://diy.geschool.net

• Asesmen Kompetensi Minimum:

https://github.com/AKM-geschool

• Skor Digital Pencak Silat:

https://github.com/New-Skordigital

• Dribble (Design UI/UX):

https://dribbble.com/Evi annisa

Skills and Interests

Skills: HTML CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React Js, GIT, UI/UX Design (Figma)

Language: Indonesian **Tools:** VsCode and Figma

Interests: Drawing, Music, Gaming, Reading and Writing, Coding